question_data = [
        {"category": "General Knowledge",
         "type": "boolean",
         "difficulty": "medium",
         "question": "There are 86400 seconds in a day.",
         "correct_answer": "True",
         "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
        {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
         "question": "An eggplant is a vegetable.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
        {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
         "question": "The bikini is named after the Bikini Atoll, "
                     "an island where the United States conducted tests on atomic bombs.",
         "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
        {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
         "question": "You are allowed to sell your soul on eBay.", "correct_answer": "False",
         "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
                                          "question": "Kissing someone for one minute burns about 2 calories.",
                                          "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
        {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
         "question": "The French word to travel is &quot;Travail&quot;", "correct_answer": "False",
         "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
                                          "question": "Albert Einstein had trouble with mathematics when he was in school.",
                                          "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
        {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
         "question": "Haggis is traditionally ate on Burns Night.", "correct_answer": "True",
         "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
                                           "question": "Francis Bacon died from a fatal case of pneumonia while he was attempting to preserve meat by stuffing a chicken with snow.",
                                           "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
        {"category": "General Knowledge", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
         "question": "Instant mashed potatoes were invented by Canadian Edward Asselbergs in 1962.",
         "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}
    ]
